<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Assist</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="long_text">Material is the metaphor For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere"when a user tries to pick up one of cards.Material is the metaphor For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere"when a user tries to pick up one of cards.
        Material is thinterfample, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere"when a user tries to pick up one of cards</string>

    <string name="already_have_account"><u>Already have account</u></string>
    <string name="dont_have_account"><u>Do not have account?</u></string>
    <string name="forgot_password"><u>Forgot Password</u></string>
    <string-array name="quick_credits_type">
        <item>KopasAids Loans for Corp Members</item>
        <item>Civil Servants Loans</item>

    </string-array>

    <string name="booking_payment">1. Before you make the payment, ensure that you have already inspected the apartment and that you like what you saw.\n\n

2. Ensure to carry out your due diligence on the apartment.\n\n

3. Make sure to ask questions regarding the Light bills, water bills and any other services provided in the apartment and that you are okay with all the bills/charges.\n\n

4. Make sure to reach an agreement with the apartment owner or their authorised representative to complete every structural repair if there is any, before Seven(7) days from the moment you made this payment.\n\n

4a. In a situation where the apartment owner or their authorised representative fails to honour their part of the agreement you both had\n\n

4b. You can request a refund within seven(7) days from the day this rent is paid.\n\n

Note: The equivalent of Seven(7) days of rent will be deducted from the amount you paid before refunding the rest to you.\n\n

        To Apply for a Refund\n
Open the App, From the home screen Click on Accommodation > Show Bookings > Select the apartment > Apply for Refund.\n\n
    </string>

    <string name="acc_warning">
        Your safety and security of your money are extremely important to us,  therefore, we strongly recommend that; \n\n

1. You do not engage in any cash transactions with the agent outside this platform.\n\n

2. You should not schedule an inspection at odd hours or at night.\n\n

3. Ensure to deal directly with the agent above or their authorized representative, do not engage with any unknowing third party.\n\n
    </string>

    <string-array name="quick_credit_loan_amount">
        <item>NGN10,000</item>
        <item>NGN20,000</item>
        <item>NGN30,000</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="loan_payback_period">
        <item>1month</item>
        <item>2months</item>
        <item>3months</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
